Why don't you sit on it?
See if it fits.
Annie's chair
is indeed a little hard.
But the size is quite right.
Thanks to you.
It's you
who started this storm,
putting the company in jeopardy.
But
there has to be someone to steer the ship.
To live is to face death.
Nothing can be established without being destroyed.
Isn't it?
Just say it.
You come to me today
to talk about the proposal of the charity fund, right?
Your idea is bold
and smart.
It maximizes the recovery of
the company's reputation at its lowest ebb.
and if executed properly,
it could also be a highly talked-about large-scale marketing campaign.
I can approve it.
As expected,
in the eyes of a pure capitalist,
everything can be turned into business.
But you would just nod so easily,
which doesn't seem like your style.
Five years,
ten percent of annual profit
will be invested in your fund.
Five years
are enough to reshape the brand image
and build confidence in the capital market.
That's the bottom line.
I want 90%.
Jiang Li,
when Annie can't protect herself
and can't exercise her shareholder rights,
I
am the one
with the most say here.
You have no bargaining chips
to negotiate with me.
It seems that you have forgotten
who made it possible
for you to be here.
Well said.
In the business world,
sacrificing pawns is common.
What matters most is
who wins
in the end.
will be me.
I can destroy the Lu family and Annie,
and there are many ways to dismantle Golden Thread.
Oh,
are you threatening me?
I'm just reminding you,
if this company
can't atone for the sins of Annie,
then it has no reason to exist.
No need to make it so complicated.
This is a 20% share transfer agreement
of Morgan's shares.
Now,
I'm the holder.
Impossible.
I've confirmed with Morgan.
They won't easily give up these core shares.
What if the conditions I offered
are too good to refuse?
Alright.
Tell me what conditions
you offered them
that they can't refuse.
The entire equity of Ruisheng Technology under my name.
The entire equity?
What?
Are you kidding me?
You're trading a tech company valued at billions
for a 20% equity in the shaky Golden Thread?
Are you crazy?
Sister-in-law,
I told you long ago,
if you're against Jiang Li,
I want to try
to fight with all my strength.
If you still want to struggle,
I'll accompany you to the end.
Fine.
Even if you hold 20% of the equity
to support her proposal,
according to her plan,
90% of the annual profit
of Golden Thread will be used for charity.
It's like weaning a baby from breastfeeding.
Golden Thread will collapse sooner or later.
Sister-in-law,
I'm not a capitalist,
and I'm not interested in business.
Weighing the pros and cons,
calculating gains and losses,
are never
important to me.
Are you crazy?
[31.8 yuan paid.]
What's wrong?
Why didn't you tell me
you ran away from the hospital?
I...
I just woke up and
came to see you.
You ran away from the hospital?
Go back after dinner.
Okay.
Ruisheng Technology is worth billions.
and you just gave it away like that?
Was it really worth it?
If I hadn't done this,
would you have tried everything,
even risking your life,
just to walk away unharmed,
put a period on your dark past,
and let you stand in the light again?
It's just a small company. What's the big deal?
I read your diary.
Ah?
You've read it all?
When did you read it?
I...
Do you think...
Why are you here?
Where's Lu Qianqian?
She can't come.
Seeing her mother stabbed by you,
it caused her
great trauma.
The doctor said
she might need a long time
to recover psychologically.
And she may never recover.
What about Mumu?
Who's taking care of
my son?
Of course, it's me, his
legally recognized biological father.
Mumu is my son.
He's the son of Lu Qianqian and me.
Lu Xu,
not to mention how many years you'll be sentenced for this.
Ten years?
Or 20 years?
Even if you are released from prison one day,
when you see the grown-up Mumu,
what do you expect him to call you?
I'm afraid
he can only call you uncle.
Zhou Jian,
you are truly despicable to the core.
Indeed.
Raising
the child of the person who dragged me into the abyss
as if he's my own flesh and blood
is the biggest punishment for me.
And you
can never
tell him who you are openly.
You can never give him
as a father.
This is the biggest punishment for you.
I forgot to tell you.
Mumu has changed his name.
From now on,
he's called Zhou Mu.
Congratulations.
Jiang Li,
your plan is completed.
You've completely ruined the Lu family,
and broken.
Are you satisfied?
Thank you.
Lu Xu,
you woke up long ago,
didn't you?
What did you tell him?
I just told him the truth.
What truth?
About you,
about him,
about Annie,
and about the Lu family.
The dirtiest and funniest truth.
Back then, Grandpa Lu and Annie had a business marriage.
They were like oil and water.
Each had their own lover,
and each had a child.
The funniest thing is
the due dates of these two children are on the same day.
I know that.
But there's something else you don't know.
Grandpa Lu's mistress gave birth to a boy,
while Annie gave birth to a girl.
Lu Xu's mother died of postpartum hemorrhage,
and Grandpa Lu was diagnosed with cancer.
So he set up a perfect trap for Annie.
He switched the two babies
when Annie was unconscious,
and sent you to the orphanage
to be raised by Dean Li.
He told Dean Li not to stop Annie from adopting you.
To get the 30% inheritance
from Grandpa Lu's will,
Annie went to the orphanage to adopt you.
Annie has been calculating
and fighting for a lifetime.
She has been working hard for others.
She even diluted and transferred her own daughter's shares
to that substitute.
You come here today
just to tell me this?
If you're done,
please leave now.
I don't want to see you anymore.
By the way,
I forgot to tell you something.
I know
you were the one who stabbed Annie that day.
And Lu Xu
just took the blame for you.